Let us now talk about Bootstrap support for forms.
接下来让我们学习一下 Bootstrap 对表格的支持
In particular,
在 bootstrap 中
the various classes that Bootstrap provides in order to style the forms.
来实现不同风格的表格
We have seen forms already in a lot of detail, in the previous course.
我们之前已经学习过了许多和表格有关的知识
So in this lecture, I will primarily deal with Bootstrap's
所以在这节课 我会着重讲解
own classes that are available to style the forms.
Bootstrap 的各种类以及对应的不同风格的表格
Forms in Bootstrap are created using the form tags.
在 Bootstrap 中 表格是通过 form 标签来创建的
So all the elements of the form are enclosed inside the form tags.
表格中的所有元素都会被封装在 一个 form 标签下
If we do not specify any class for the form, then the standard layout for
如果我们不对表格指定任何一个类
the form is used.
那么 Bootstrap 会选择应用默认格式的表格
We can specify the form class as form-horizontal.
我们可以用 form-horizontal 来定制一个表格
And if we do that, then we can have the labels
如果我们这样做了 那么标签将会
to be displayed to the left side of the data entry fields.
在输入框的左侧显示
So as you see in this particular example, when you specify
正如这个例子所示 我们用 form-group
a label together with the data entry element,
同时实现了一个标签和一个输入框
then we would use a form-group to enclose these two.
并将它们封装在了一起
So in here, I am specifying the label as the first name there,
这里我将标签内容设置为了 First Name
which is shown in the form on the left hand side.
它显示在了表格的左侧
To the right of it in the same horizontal line,
而右侧的同一水平线上
the actual field for entering the data is shown.
则是一个输入框
Now by default within Bootstrap,
于是我们发现 Bootstrap 默认设置中
the form group supports the row class.
form-group 是拥有对 row 类的支持的
So inside the form group, you can use the column classes
所以在 form-group 里面我们可以使用 column 类
in order to style the elements inside the form group.
来排列好 form-group 中的元素
So here, you see me using the column class for both the label as well as for
你可以看到我对标签和输入框
the input element there.
都应用了 column 类
We can also define inline forms.
我们还可以定义同行表格
Inline forms are shown completely in a single line.
同行表格将会在一行内显示其所有内容
So this could be very useful, for example,
这是很有用的功能
if you want to include in your navbar a method for
比如说 它可以让你的导航栏
the user to type in their username and password and log in to your website.
支持用户在其中输入账户密码来登录
So inline forms use the class form-inline, and
行内表格是通过 class="form-inline" 来实现的
inside there you can specify the form groups.
在其中你可以指定一些 form-group
In particular, in this example, you see that for the label
而在这个栗子里 我对一些 label 标签
tag, I am specifying the class as sr-only,
指定了一个 sr-only 类
meaning that those labels are valid only for screen readers.
表示这些标签只有在用户使用屏幕阅读器时才能看到
Now for a normal visual display, those labels will be hidden.
对于一般的情况 这些标签将会被隐藏
Instead, we are using the placeholder inside the form element itself
而作为代替 我们可以使用 placeholder 属性
to identify what the user is supposed to type into that field in the form.
来告诉用户这个输入框是干嘛用的
Another class that Bootstrap supports is called as an input-group.
另一个 Bootstrap 支持的类叫 input-group
An input-group allows you to group together a set of elements.
它允许你将一系列元素组合起来
Now, for any data entry field that you have within your form,
而且对于你表格中的任何一个输入框
you can also have an input-group-addon, so
你都可以用 input-group-addon 来在其左或右侧
that you can add elements to the left and right side of your group.
加入一些元素
So in this example, you see me including the left and
在这个例子里 我就在用户输入地区编码的输入框左右
right parenthesis to the field where I allow the user to type in an area code.
加了一对括号
Say, for example, a telephone number.
这个地区编码可以用来加在电话号码前面
So in here, I am attaching using the input-group-addon the left parentheses,
你可以看到 我同时对左括号和右括号
and the input-group-addon the right parentheses for this group.
应用了 input-group-addon
So these group addons, I am taking the help of a div to
需要注意的是
put them together with my field there.
这些类需应用到一个 div 中
Now, we'll move on to the next exercise,
接下来我们需要完成一个练习
where we'll continue to work on our website.
在这个练习里我们将会在我们的网页中
We're gonna add buttons to the web site, and
加入一些按钮
also use various form elements in order to create
和表格来允许用户
a user feedback form for our restaurant.
给我们的餐厅做出反馈 【翻译 - Carefree0910】